Guide to the Glenda Joe / Houston Asian American community advocacy and festival arts records, circa 1980-2015 MS 667
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IX: Great Wall Communications records and television recordings
  - Subseries B: Television clips on videotape (VHS) (Box 15, Box 16)
    - U.T. racist allegations, 1997-01-04
    - HPD officer of the year, 1997-04-26
    - China take-over of Hong Kong and mayoral race, 1997-06-30-1997-07-05
    - Mayoral endorsement, 1997-12-04
    - GWE/TMP metro psa Vietnamese
    - VoTexas
    - Glenda Joe
    - Asian heritage, 1998-05-10
    - Clinton visit, 1998-06-02-1998-06-06
    - Clinton visit, 1998-06-02
    - City health department complaint, 1998-06-24-1998-06-29
    - Portrait of a people:Houston's Asian American Community, 1998-10-18
    - Chinatown, 1999-04-21
    - HPD "join the force"
    - HPD recruitment "join the force"
    - Interviews Glenda and Sonny
    - A tapestry of Asia
    - Glenda Joe- election
    - Ann Deveare Smith on "race"
    - POV Vi Chin, 2001
    - Asian conference
    - Dad's movie
    - Glenda Joe's Houston
    - First day of the future
    - Fires in the mirror
    - Man Troung extradition hearing
    - Club case s.coast copy
    - Glenda ch.8 Robert Newberry
    - Stock ticken
    - Asian town hall meeting and cultural festival
    - City council
- Series X: Martha Wong ethics complaint
  - "FYI" faxes to reporters/colleagues (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Evidentiary hearing, 1995-06-26-1995-06-29 (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
  - Martha Wong events (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Wong financial/campaign contribution records, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Gordon Quan conflict, 1995-05-1995-07 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Asian American heritage association conflict, 1992-05-1995-02 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Complaints about Martha Wong, 1995-08-1995-10 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Martha Wong ethics complaint- news clippings, 1993-12-05-1996-03-06 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Song about Martha Wong (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Handwritten note fragments (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Pre-ethics committee hearing, 1992-05-1995-03 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - City Council statement by Glenda Joe re Martha Wong, 1994-12-13 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Ethics committee hearing- preparation, 1995-03-1995-05-25 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Formal complaints, drafts, 1995-02-1995-04 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Ethics committee procedures (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Ethics committee hearing + results, 1995-05-25 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Packages of documents to be distributed "Tora Docs" - correspondence and notes (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Series XI: Correspondence
  - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2008 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Series XII: Glenda Joe awards and recognitions
  - Outstanding Young Women of America, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Certificate of appreciation presented by the Houston Independent School District to Glenda Joe for participation on the Task Force for Educational Excellence, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - State of Texas hereby presents this certificate of appreciation to Glenda Kay Joe for expectional and distinguished volunteer service, 1983-12-09 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Marquis Who's Who publications board certificate Who's Who of American women, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Leadership Texas seminars certificate of completion, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Glenda Kay Joe as a distinguished member of the faculty of Business Volunteers for the Arts/Houston with all the honors, rights, and privileges appertaining thereto, 1987-04-09 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Central Houston, Inc. The University of Events Citation of Appreciation, 1987-06-11 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - The Marquis Who's Who publications board certificate Who's Who of American women, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - For Working Wonders The United Way, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Certificate of appreciation, may it be known that Glenda Joe was the guest speaker at the Houston Central Lions, 1988-01-26 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Acres Homes Citizens chamber of commerce business supporting business certificate of appreciation presented to The Council of Asian American Organizations, 1990-10-04 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Acres Homes Citizens chamber of commerce business suporting business certificate of appreciation, 1990-10-04 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Certificate of appreciation census, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Certificate of appreciation from the City of Houston presented to Glenda Joe for meritorious service to the community, 1990-05-02 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Thanks to Glenda Joe in the 1990-1991 United Way Campaign (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Enron Corporation Brotherhood Month certificate of appreciation, 1992-03-05 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Appreciation of devoted and invaluable services for Taiwanese Association of American- summer conference, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Certificate of recognition presented to Glenda Joe in recognition of your contribution to Women's history month, 1993-03-24 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Certificate of appreciation for participating in National Asian/Pacific Islander month celebration, 1993-05-25 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Acres Homes Citizens chamber of commerce business supporting business resolution member of the year, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Certificate of appreciation presented to Glenda Joe for services rendered as a grand juror of Harris County State of Texas, 1994-04-29 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Harris county sheriff's department this is to certify that Glenda Joe has been appointed an Honorary deputy sheriff in Harris County, Texas and is entitled to receive all the privileges and benefits of this department, 1994-04-29 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Certificate of recognition from the office of John W. Peavy, Jr. to Glenda Joe, recipient of the 1995 south central YMCA seventh annual "Tribute to Leadership award", 1995-04-13 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - "Emiliano Zapata" award, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - The Houston area women's center presents this certificate of appreciation to Glenda Joe in recognition of committed and dedicated service, 1996-04-01 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Certificate of appreciation for continued committment from the police advisory committee, 1996-09-18 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Certificate of appreciation from the city of Houston presented to Glenda Joe for leadership and volunteerism in hosting Houston's first Asian-American officer of the year awards ceremony, 1997-10-09 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Certificate of appreciation from the office of Carroll G. Robinson presented to Glenda Joe in appreciation of your participation in the Teen Leadership Summit, 1998-11-07 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - City of Houston extends congratulations and best wishes to Glenda Joe in recognition as an EEOC 40TH anniversary "All Star", 2005-07-13 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Certificate of congressional recognition presented to Glenda Joe "Houston EEOC'S 40th anniversary all-stars", 2005-07-13 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Certificate of special congressional recognition presented to Glenda Joe in honor of recognition as a honoree by the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 2005-07-13 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - B'nai B'rith Forest of Peace in Israel in appreciation to Glenda Kay Joe from Julius Israel Lodge B'nai B'rith (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Recent awards Great Wall Enterprises (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Thank you award proudly presented to Glenda Kay Joe for working wonders The United Way (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - U.S. Department of Justice community relations service certificate of particpation to Glenda Joe for significant contributions to The Southeast Asian Gulf Coast Network Seminar, 1993-08-30-1993-08-31 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Harris County Psychiatric Center gratefully acknowledges the contributions of Glenda Joe to the National Symposium, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Community service appreciation award presented to Glenda Joe Council of Asian American Organizations in recognition of your outstanding service and dedication to the Vietnamese American community in Houston by The Vietnamese American Community of Houston and vicinity, 1997-06-22 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Houston Community College system central college leadership award presented to Glenda Joe for outstanding service to the Vietnamese Students' Organization, 1996-05-31 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Outstanding girl in drama, 1969-1970 (Box 23)
  - Presented to Glenda Kay Joe in sincere appreciation and recognition of distinguished service, loyalty and devotion to the objects and furtherance of Lionism. Houston Vietnam Lions Club, 1990 (Box 23)
  - American Theatrical Ensemble, Inc. Les Rendez- Vous De Les Chattes Day Emma Sanders Award to Glenda Joe, 1994-03-20 (Box 23)
  - Acres Homes Citizens chamber of commerce "a people building community" leadership Great Wall Enterprises, 1993 (Box 23)
  - Texas Executive Women Women on the move Glenda Joe, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Reconocimiento especial en honor de Glenda Joe C.A.D.P.C, 1994-10-1996-10 (Box 23)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Unity Award, 1993 (Box 23)
  - JACL National security through unity Glenda K. Joe Edison Uno Civil Rights award in recognition of outstanding contributions and leadership in civil rights presented by the Japanese American Citizens League, 1994-08-05 (Box 23)
  - Chinese Women of America Houston Public Libraries exhibit poster, 1984-11-13-1984-12-28 (Box 23)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson Space Center certificate of appreciation, 1993-05 (Box 23)